(Mary Cooper:)Thank you for picking me up.
(Sheldon:)Oh, you're welcome.
(Mary:)I was speaking to
your young lady.
(Amy:)My pleasure, Mrs. Cooper.
(Mary:)Oh, please call me Mary.
(Amy:)Okay, Mary.
(Penny:)You know,
that doesn't work for me,
(Sheldon:)let's stay with Mrs. Cooper.
(Mary:)Sheldon, don't be silly.
Wait, what?
(Sheldon:)That's what I called you
till I got to know you better.
(Mary:)It was so nice of Leonard
and Penny to invite me.
(Sheldon:)Well, actually, I...
It sure was.
(Mary:)I've always had a special place
in my heart for Leonard.
(Mary:)Taking care of my baby
all these years.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me,
I take care of him.
(Mary:)Sure you do.
(Mary:)So who else is coming
to this shindig?
(Amy:)Oh, well, the usual gang.
(Amy:)Penny's family
is coming tomorrow.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, and Leonard's mother's
already here.
(Mary:)Oh, Beverly.
(Mary:)How nice.
(Amy:)You've met her, right?
(Mary:)Yes, I have.